[{"answer": "Today, not in that situation, but in Joplin on Sunday, yes.", "docId": "110524pmt", "aSentId": 66, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 65}, {"answer": "It's bad today.", "docId": "110524pmt", "aSentId": 75, "question": "How bad is this situation that's now enveloping this region?", "qSentId": 74}, {"answer": "Good evening, Piers.", "docId": "110524pmt", "aSentId": 89, "question": "Sam, what's the latest?", "qSentId": 88}, {"answer": "We really don't.", "docId": "110524pmt", "aSentId": 112, "question": "Do you have any clue as to where he may be?", "qSentId": 111}, {"answer": "I mean, we know for sure that they pulled into that grocery store parking lot, because they couldn't see where they were going.", "docId": "110524pmt", "aSentId": 119, "question": "What do you think may have happened?", "qSentId": 118}, {"answer": "I'm sorry, on 20th and Wisconsin is the corner where the car was --", "docId": "110524pmt", "aSentId": 138, "question": "On 20th Street?", "qSentId": 137}, {"answer": "No -- well, really his last memory was just of the windows breaking and that's it.", "docId": "110524pmt", "aSentId": 142, "question": "And Lantz's friend is Jonathan Taylor, and his last memory is that he may be still alive, he thinks?", "qSentId": 141}, {"answer": "It's gone.", "docId": "110524pmt", "aSentId": 253, "question": "Is it completely gone?", "qSentId": 252}, {"answer": "It's pretty terrifying.", "docId": "110524pmt", "aSentId": 318, "question": "How do you feel?", "qSentId": 317}, {"answer": "My heart pretty much stopped, because, I mean, we've gone there for four years.", "docId": "110524pmt", "aSentId": 326, "question": "Elizabeth, when you saw the pictures of the school, what went through your mind?", "qSentId": 325}, {"answer": "Well, shortly after we had to go get our diplomas, one of our senior principal actually said that there was a tornado watch, and that everyone should be careful and he was -- he was just telling us to keep check on the weather and if we were going to go home, to go home directly.", "docId": "110524pmt", "aSentId": 331, "question": "When did you become aware about what was happening?", "qSentId": 330}, {"answer": "Frankly, I took it as another, oh, well, it's another warning.", "docId": "110524pmt", "aSentId": 336, "question": "Did you see it as real, or did it all just seem like, oh, well, it's just another warning?", "qSentId": 335}, {"answer": "I'm going to Ozark Christian College here at Joplin, and it didn't get affected by the tornado at all, because it's on the north end of Joplin.", "docId": "110524pmt", "aSentId": 340, "question": "Do you know what you're going to be doing?", "qSentId": 339}, {"answer": "Well, a lot of us are in shock, because we've always been, like, oh, Joplin is always the place where the tornado misses or we've always been like, oh, nothing ever happens in Joplin.", "docId": "110524pmt", "aSentId": 348, "question": "How would you describe the mood?", "qSentId": 347}, {"answer": "It is.", "docId": "110524pmt", "aSentId": 354, "question": "It's heartbreaking, isn't it?", "qSentId": 353}, {"answer": "Rob, if you can stand by for us.", "docId": "110524pmt", "aSentId": 413, "question": "Piers?", "qSentId": 412}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, I can tell you, I just got back from Alabama, it seems like yesterday, and it never ceases to amaze me, the destruction is just epic.", "docId": "110524pmt", "aSentId": 425, "question": "Given other scenes you've had to go and help at, how does this rank?", "qSentId": 424}, {"answer": "Well, let me, first of all, go ahead and make a comparison.", "docId": "110524pmt", "aSentId": 431, "question": "So we can get a sense of the scale of this, what do you do to commence this rescue operation?", "qSentId": 430}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110524pmt", "aSentId": 444, "question": "Are you impressed by the speed of the response?", "qSentId": 443}, {"answer": "Well, we've already seen tornadoes that have dropped big tornadoes across Oklahoma, at least four fatalities near Oklahoma City.", "docId": "110524pmt", "aSentId": 470, "question": "What do you think we can expect?", "qSentId": 469}, {"answer": "Yes, and you know Piers, after an incident like this, a disaster like this, often, you know, there's adrenaline and the adrenaline carries you through.", "docId": "110524pmt", "aSentId": 526, "question": "I mean, it's just been decimated, hasn't it?", "qSentId": 525}, {"answer": "Yes, indeed.", "docId": "110524pmt", "aSentId": 547, "question": "You think it's irresponsible for President Obama to say that?", "qSentId": 546}]